indimedicos.com 2010-01-10

# IndiMedicos - India's best community for doctors | Privacy Policy | Create Professional Network and connect with MD,Surgenons,Cardiologists,Orthopaeidcs across India

IndiMedicos - Privacy Policy

IndiMedicos takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

 **What this Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This Privacy Policy covers IndiMedicos’s treatment of personally identifiable information that IndiMedicos collects when you are on the IndiMedicos site, and when you use IndiMedicos’s services. This policy also covers IndiMedicos's treatment of any personally identifiable information that IndiMedicos's business partners share with IndiMedicos.
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that IndiMedicos does not own or control, or to people that IndiMedicos does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

  * IndiMedicos collects personally identifiable information when you register for a IndiMedicos account, when you use certain IndiMedicos products or services, when you visit IndiMedicos pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. IndiMedicos may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.
  * When you register with IndiMedicos, we ask for your name, email address, birth date, gender and personal interests. Once you register with IndiMedicos and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
  * IndiMedicos also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, IndiMedicos cookie information and the page you requested.
  * In addition, when you use IndiMedicos's services, you may make some of your personal information public. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return and IndiMedicos will not be responsible for the use or misuse of such information.
  * IndiMedicos uses information for three general purposes: to customize the content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services promoted by IndiMedicos or other companies, and to contact you about specials and new products. IndiMedicos is not responsible for the accuracy, completeness, veracity and reliability of any targeted content, products and services which may be accessed or advertised to you and IndiMedicos will not be liable for any loss or damage arising out of the same.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * IndiMedicos will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.
  * IndiMedicos will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:

o We have your consent to share the information;  
o We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;  
o We need to share the information with certain service partners in order to respond to your comments or to resolve service issues. (Unless we tell you differently, these partners have no independent right to use this information except to respond to your comments or to resolve the service issues.);  
o We respond to requests from any Indian or foreign government, security, defence, revenue, regulatory or other authority, agency or officer;  
o We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or  
o We find that your actions on our web sites violate the IndiMedicos Terms of Service or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

 **Cookies**

  * IndiMedicos may set and access IndiMedicos cookies on your computer and you may not be able to disable these cookies. IndiMedicos ensures that all information collected and accessed by IndiMedicos through the access of these cookies will be maintained in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
  * IndiMedicos allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to IndiMedicos's cookies.
  * IndiMedicos uses web beacons to access our cookies within our network of web sites and in connection with IndiMedicos products and services.

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

  * IndiMedicos gives you the ability to edit your IndiMedicos Account Information and preferences at any time, including whether you want IndiMedicos to contact you about specials and new products. IndiMedicos is not responsible and will not be liable for the accuracy, completeness, veracity and reliability of any information including any customized information which may be accessed by or provided to you, which could vary depending on your IndiMedicos Account Information and preferences including your browser preferences.
  * You may request deletion of your IndiMedicos account by visiting our Account Deletion page, verifying your password once more and confirming your choice to terminate the account. Please click here to read about what information may possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted.

**Security**

  * Your IndiMedicos Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security.
  * In certain areas IndiMedicos uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * IndiMedicos may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
